The Huntington Library
Arthur M. Ellis Collection of Photographic Negatives
- Container List
  - Assessment, page 6 on, 1850; [Almost entire book was photographed but some pages are missing.] (Box 28, Item 1865-1873)
  - Sketches of battlefields; 1850 and 1852 California county divisions, undated; [Renderings.] (Box 28, Item 1874-1877)
  - Los Angeles County. Court and legal documents and letters, 1850-1854; 1880,; 1908,; undated (Box 28, Item 1878-1897)
  - Orange County. Santa Ana street scenes, buildings, and residences, 1873; 1898,; undated (Box 28, Item 1898-1906)
  - Orange County. Santa Ana scenes and residences, including Santa Ana Depot, Opera House, undated (Box 29, Item 1907-1911)
  - Orange County. Anaheim street scenes and buildings; Anaheim Landing, undated (Box 29, Item 1912-1922)
  - Orange County. Buena Park; Fullerton; Miscellaneous, undated (Box 29, Item 1923-1929)
  - Riverside County. Tibbetts property; Lake Elsinore, 1923; undated (Box 29, Item 1930-1932)
  - San Bernardino County. Includes city of San Bernardino buildings and street scenes, 1873-1874; 1883,; undated; [Includes photographs taken by W.A. Vale.] (Box 29, Item 1933-1948)
  - San Diego, 1872; undated; [Includes photographs taken by J.C. Parker.] (Box 29, Item 1949-1951)
  - San Diego buildings and street scenes; Views of San Diego Harbor; Drawings from Phoenixiana; Other miscellaneous, 1874; undated; [Includes photographs taken by J.C. Parker.] (Box 30, Item 1952-1977)
  - Ventura County and Paso Robles, including Camulos Ranch, undated (Box 30, Item 1978-1980)
  - Santa Barbara and Santa Barbara County, undated (Box 30, Item 1981-1984)
  - City of Monterey, buildings and homes, 1850; undated (Box 30, Item 1985-1991)
  - Santa Cruz County. Benicia and Big Basin, 1857; 1918, undated; undated (Box 30, Item 1992-1997)
  - Santa Cruz County. Big Basin; Santa Cruz; Other miscellaneous, ca. 1856; 1918,; undated (Box 31, Item 1998-2003)
  - San Francisco and Petaluma drawings and photos, includes Baldwin Hotel, M.G. Vallejo Adobe, 1849; 1865,; undated (Box 31, Item 2004-2011)
  - San Diego Mission and surrounding grounds, 1874; undated; [Includes photographs taken by J.C. Parker.] (Box 31, Item 2012-2023)
  - San Gabriel Mission, undated (Box 31, Item 2024-2027)
  - Missions. San Buenaventura; Soledad; San Juan, 1874; undated (Box 31, Item 2028-2032)
  - Mission photos from Vischer and McPherson, organized by Elliss numbering, undated (Box 31, Item 2033-2036)
  - Mission photos from Vischer and McPherson (continued), organized by Elliss numbering, undated (Box 32, Item 2037-2041)
  - Gold Rush and emigration, Sutters Fort and various mining camps; Emigrant trail; Miscellaneous, 1852; 1875,; 1918,; undated (Box 32, Item 2042-2059)
  - Stage Coaches, wagon teams, wagon trains, 1894; undated (Box 32, Item 2060-2071)
  - Central Pacific Railroad trains and routes, undated (Box 32, Item 2072-2076)
  - Southern Pacific Railroad locomotives; Newhall tunnel, undated (Box 33, Item 2077-2079a)
  - Miscellaneous transportation. Boats; Autos; Bicycle, 1900; undated (Box 33, Item 2080-2083)
  - Vischer illustrations arranged according to Elliss numbering, 1860s-1870s; 1891,; undated (Box 33, Item 2084-2109)
  - Vischer illustrations. Locations from Orange County to Paso Robles, 1860s; undated (Box 33, Item 2110-2123)
  - Vischer illustrations. Mountain trails and stage coach, 1860s; 1870s,; undated (Box 34, Item 2124-2131)
  - Miscellaneous illustrations, 1870; undated (Box 34, Item 2132-2132a)
  - Portraits and people by name. Alexander through Dorsey, undated (Box 34, Item 2133-2164)
  - Portraits and people by name. Dreher through Lugo, 1864; 1890,; 1922-1923,; undated (Box 35, Item 2165-2210)
  - Portraits and people by name. Lugo through Stockton, 1855; 1921,; undated (Box 36, Item 2211-2254)
  - Portraits and people by name. Stowall through Yount, 1860; undated (Box 37, Item 2255-2277)
  - Portraits and people. Unidentified women, undated (Box 37, Item 2278-2282c)
  - Portraits and people. Unidentified men, undated (Box 37, Item 2283-2293)
  - Portraits and people. Unidentified men; Group photos, undated (Box 38, Items 2293a-2299d)
  - Pen sketches of early prominent Jewish citizens of Los Angeles, undated (Box 39, Item 2300-2304)
  - Native Americans. Portraits and group photos, undated (Box 39, Item 2305-2314)
  - Native Americans. Artifacts and structures, including petroglyphs and sweat houses, undated (Box 39, Item 2315-2325)
  - U.S. history. Sites; Artifacts; Portraits, includes George Washington and Benjamin Foster, undated (Box 39, Item 2326-2336a)
  - U.S. history. Sites; Artifacts; Portraits including Benjamin Foster, undated (Box 39, Item 2337-2339)
  - U.S. hitory. Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 40, Items 2340-2345p)
  - U.S. history. Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 41, Items 2345q-2345ee)
  - U.S. history. Abraham Lincoln portraits and sites; Kit Carson; White House, undated (Box 42, Item 2346-2358)
  - Freemasonry. Lodges; Artifacts; Book passages; Miscellaneous, 1851; 1856,; 1908,; undated (Box 42, Item 2359-2370)
  - Miscellaneous scenery and locations outside of California, undated (Box 42, Item 2371-2380c)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 43, Item 2381-2385)
  - Miscellaneous. Book passages; Clippings; Printing, undated; [No. 2395c removed for conservation.] (Box 43, Item 2386-2395g)
  - Miscellaneous. Unidentified locations, undated (Box 43, Item 2396-2413)
  - Miscellaneous. Unidentified buildings, houses, landscapes, undated (Box 44, Item 2414-2458)
  - Miscellaneous. Unidentified buildings, houses, landscapes, undated (Box 45, Items 2458a-2458i)
  - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfrey s numbers. Central Los Angeles, 1860; undated (Box 46, Item 2459-2482)
  - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfreys numbers. Rubottom property, Spadra, 1874; undated (Box 46, Item 2483-2486)
  - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfreys numbers. Central Los Angeles; L.J. Rose residence in San Gabriel, 1872; 1874,; undated (Box 46, Item 2487-2495)
  - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfreys numbers. San Luis Rey and San Juan Capistrano Missions, undated (Box 47, Item 2496-2499)
  - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfreys numbers. San Gabriel Valley, undated (Box 47, Item 2500-2512)
  - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfreys numbers. Miscellaneous Los Angeles and Los Angeles County, 1874; undated (Box 47, Item 2513-2520)
  - W.M. Godfrey photographs. Unnumbered miscellaneous Central Los Angeles and San Pedro, 1860; undated (Box 47, Item 2521-2529)
  - 5 x 7 inch glass negatives. Unidentified, undated (Box 47, Item 2530-2535)
  - 5 x 7 inch film negatives; one print. Brick building; unidentified man, undated (Box 47, Item 2536-2537)
  - 8 x 10 inch glass plate negatives, 1849-1923 (Box 48-58, Items 268-1189)
    [Prints of these items are available as viewing surrogates.]
  - 8 x 10 inch film negatives, 1849-1923; [Prints of these items are available as viewing surrogates.] (Box 59-67, Items 40-1262)
- Geographical List
  - Central Los Angeles and vicinity
    - Los Angeles County. Cahuenga Valley; Echo Park area, ca. 1886-1897; undated; [Includes photographs taken by William H. Fletcher.] (Box 3, Item 305-317B)
    - Central Los Angeles street views, 1854; 1887-1898,; undated; [Includes photographs taken by William H. Fletcher.] (Box 3, Folder 318-341)
    - Central Los Angeles streets and residences; Central Park, 1885-1912; undated; [Includes photographs taken by William H. Fletcher.] (Box 3, Folder 353-365)
    - Central Los Angeles street scenes, 1902-1918; undated (Box 3, Folder 366-395)
    - Central Los Angeles. Municipal buildings; Commercial buildings; Churches, ca. 1915; undated (Box 4, Item 396-428)
    - Central Los Angeles residences; Plaza area, 1861-1885; undated (Box 4, Item 449-477)
    - Los Angeles Plaza area, 1857-1895; undated (Box 4, Item 478-501)
    - Central Los Angeles. Bird's-eye views; Buildings, 1856-1894; undated (Box 4, Item 502-521)
    - Central Los Angeles. Schools and clubs; Parades; Parks, 1871-1899; undated (Box 4, Item 522-546)
    - Central Los Angeles street scenes, 1860-1921; undated (Box 5, Item 547-576)
    - Los Angeles. Street scenes; Bird's-eye views, 1857-1900; undated (Box 5, Item 577-606)
    - Schools; Campo de Cahuenga; Cahuenga Valley, 1877; 1896-1899,; undated; [Includes narratives by Otto Weid.] (Box 7, Item 893-908)
    - Hollywood, 1894-1903; 1920s,; 1930s,; undated (Box 7, Item 909-932)
    - Central Los Angeles street scenes; Construction progress on Los Angeles Railway building, 1890-1920; undated (Box 8, Item 978-1006)
    - Central Los Angeles street scenes and buildings, 1906-1923; undated (Box 8, Item 1007-1036C)
    - Central Los Angeles street scenes, 1905-1922; undated (Box 8, Item 1037-1057)
    - Central Los Angeles and vicinity. Street scenes; Residences, 1919; undated (Box 8, Item 1077-1096)
    - Central Los Angeles buildings and street scenes, 1923; undated; [No. 1216 missing as of December 2005.] (Box 10, Item 1190-1226)
    - Central Los Angeles buildings and street scenes, 1923; undated (Box 10, Item 1227-1241)
    - Los Angeles County. Gardens; Parks; Residential streets, undated (Box 10, Item 1243-1251)
    - Drawings of Los Angeles, 1850s (Box 11, Item 1264-1265a)
    - Los Angeles. Plaza; Pico House; Plaza Church, 1857; 1891,; undated (Box 11, Item 1266-1291)
    - Los Angeles. Avila Adobe/Stockton's Headquarters, undated (Box 11, Item 1292-1295)
    - Los Angeles. Sonoratown, 1875-1885; undated (Box 11, Item 1296-1399)
    - Los Angeles. Sonortatown; Chinatown/Negro Alley, 1880; undated (Box 12, Item 1300-1308)
    - Los Angeles. Businesses and street scenes along Los Angeles; 1st; Temple and Commercial Streets, 1862-1872; undated (Box 12, Item 1309-1315a)
    - Los Angeles. Abel Stearns residence, "El Palacio", 1850; undated (Box 12, Item 1316-1320)
    - Los Angeles. North Main Street, 1868-1885; undated (Box 12, Item 1321-1336)
    - Los Angeles. North Main Street; Temple Block and vicinity, 1862; undated (Box 13, Item 1337-1345)
    - Los Angeles. Temple Block, 1876; undated (Box 13, Item 1346-1351)
    - Los Angeles. Old Court House, 1868; 1875,; undated (Box 13, Item 1352-1356)
    - Los Angeles. Old Court House; Bella Union/St. Charles Hotel, photos and litho, 1858-1880; undated (Box 14, Item 1357-1365)
    - Los Angeles. Main Street between 1st and 3rd. Workmans store; Meyers residence; St. Vibianas Cathedral and views from St. Vibianas, 1870-1889; undated (Box 14, Item 1366-1379)
    - Los Angeles. Main Street between 3rd and 6th including street views and buildings; Pacific Electric Building, 1883; 1900,; 1918,; undated (Box 14, Item 1380-1386)
    - Los Angeles. Pacific Electric Building (continued); residences on Main St. (exact locations unknown), undated (Box 14, Item 1387-1390)
    - Los Angeles. Street scenes and buildings along 2nd Street; Views from 2nd Street, 1870; undated (Box 15, Item 1391-1395)
    - Los Angeles. Street scenes and buildings along Spring Street to 3rd Street including the Nadeau Block and Phillips Block; Views of the Wolfskill Ranch from Spring Street and 3rd Street, 1889; 1892,; 1912,; undated (Box 15, Item 1396-1412)
    - Los Angeles. Wolfskill Ranch orchards and fruit trees, undated (Box 15, Item 1413-1415)
    - Los Angeles. Round House and Garden of Paradise, undated (Box 15, Item 1416-1421)
    - Los Angeles. Street scenes and buildings along S. Spring Street from about 4th Street including Ralphs store, 1903; undated (Box 15, Item 1422-1426)
    - Los Angeles. Street scenes; Homes and buildings along S. Spring Street, 1875; 1889,; undated (Box 16, Item 1427-1430)
    - Los Angeles. Homes and buildings along San Pedro Street including the Lugo adobe, 1921; undated (Box 16, Item 1431-1436)
    - Los Angeles. Palm Drive; Agricultural Park; Shrine Auditorium; Chester Place, 1895; undated (Box 16, Item 1437-1440)
    - Los Angeles. Street scenes and homes on Bunker Hill and West Temple Street, including Exposition Hall, 1881; 1883,; undated (Box 16, Item 1441-1447)
    - Los Angeles. Old High School on Pound Cake Hill and views from Pound Cake Hill, 1870-1885; undated (Box 16, Item 1448-1465)
    - Los Angeles. Views from Pound Cake Hill; Red Sandstone Courthouse; St. Athenasius Church, 1891; 1895,; undated (Box 17, Item 1466-1475)
    - Los Angeles. Buildings and street scenes along Fort Street/Broadway to about 5th including Fort St. Methodist Church, old City Hall, Potomac Block, 1871; 1883-1890,; 1902-1913,; undated (Box 17, Item 1476-1506)
    - Los Angeles. Buildings and street scenes along S. Broadway from about 5th Street including Presbyterian Church, Synagogue and St. Vincent's School, 1870; 1880,; 1918,; undated (Box 18, Item 1507-1517)
    - Los Angeles. Bird's-eye views from Fort Hill; Buildings and street scenes along Hill Street, 1870; 1875,; 1910,; undated (Box 18, Item 1518-1538)
    - West Central Los Angeles. Buildings and street scenes along 4th Street and Olive Streets, 1918; undated (Box 18, Item 1539-1546)
    - West Central Los Angeles. Buildings and street scenes including the State Normal School and Hazards Pavilion, 1886; undated (Box 19, Item 1547-1555)
    - Los Angeles. Central Park and vicinity, 1881; 1885,; undated (Box 19, Item 1556-1562)
    - Los Angeles. Child's property, 1913; undated (Box 19, Item 1563-1565)
    - West Central Los Angeles. Various scenes including streets; buildings; Westlake Park and the Francisco farm, 1881-1890; undated (Box 19, Item 1566-1579)
    - Los Angeles. Farms and homes on future site of the Southern Branch of the University of California, undated (Box 19, Item 1580-1584)
    - Campo De Cahuenga, undated (Box 19, Item 1585)
    - North East and South East Central Los Angeles including Aliso Street; the Sainsevains property; Beaudry Reservoir; Boyle Heights, 1875; undated (Box 20, Item 1586-1600)
    - Los Angeles. Parades and celebrations including 4th of July, 1871 and 1894 Fiesta, 1876; undated (Box 20, Item 1601-1607)
    - Los Angeles. Hanging of Lachenais, 1871 (Box 20, Item 1608-1609a)
    - Los Angeles. Floods, 1883; undated (Box 20, Item 1610-1613)
    - Los Angeles County. Non-locational objects and unidentified locations, including "Rubbottom's bowie;" "Editorial Corps of the Weekly Comet;" Possible residences of Cameron Thom; Mayes family residence; First Ebell Club, undated (Box 24, Item 1761-1783)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified Los Angeles, undated (Box 25, Items 1783a-1783o)
    - Los Angeles County unidentified and miscellaneous includes street views, unidentified buildings and homes, engravings, 1878; undated (Box 26, Item 1784-1797)
    - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfrey 's numbers. Central Los Angeles, 1860; undated (Box 46, Item 2459-2482)
    - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfrey's numbers. Central Los Angeles, 1872; 1874,; undated (Box 46, Item 2487-2495)
    - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfrey's numbers. Miscellaneous Los Angeles and Los Angeles County, 1874; undated (Box 47, Item 2513-2520)
    - W.M. Godfrey photographs. Unnumbered miscellaneous Central Los Angeles and San Pedro, 1860; undated (Box 47, Item 2521-2529)
  - San Pedro and vicinity
    - San Pedro, 1897-1921; undated; [Includes photographs taken by William H. Fletcher.] (Box 2, Item 198-231)
    - Redondo; San Pedro, 1894-1920; undated (Box 6, Item 683-709)
    - San Pedro; Wilmington, 1850s; 1912-1917,; undated (Box 6, Item 710-729)
    - San Pedro and San Pedro Harbor, 1872; 1885,; undated (Box 23, Item 1712-1717)
    - Wilmington, including views of the town; Wilmington Exchange; Wilmington Barracks; Banning House, 1873; 1885,; 1918,; 1923,; undated (Box 23, Item 1718-1726)
    - W.M. Godfrey photographs. Unnumbered miscellaneous Central Los Angeles and San Pedro, 1860; undated (Box 47, Item 2521-2529)
  - Los Angeles County beach communities
    - Long Beach, ca. 1910-1915; undated (Box 2, Item 232-250)
    - Santa Catalina Island; Redondo Beach, ca. 1898-1910 (Box 2, Item 251-267)
    - Venice, ca. 1915; undated (Box 3, Item 268-286)
    - Santa Monica, ca. 1910; undated (Box 3, Item 287-304)
    - Railroads; Santa Monica, 1869-1923; undated (Box 5, Item 607-635)
    - Ocean Park; Venice, 1920-1923; undated (Box 5, Item 636-662)
    - Venice; Hermosa Beach, ca. 1920; undated (Box 6, Item 663-682)
    - Redondo; San Pedro, 1894-1920; undated (Box 6, Item 683-709)
    - Long Beach; Cerritos Ranch, 1870s-1918; undated; [No. 749 missing as of December 2005.] (Box 6, Item 730-757)
    - Santa Catalina Island; Huntington Beach; Newport Beach; Balboa Beach, ca. 1915-1920; undated (Box 6, Item 758-782)
    - Beach cities; Miscellaneous beaches, 1894; 1923,; undated (Box 8, Item 1058-1076)
    - Santa Monica including Santa Monica Beach and Canyon; street scenes; Santa Monica Hotel; engravings, 1872; 1878,; undated (Box 23, Item 1727-1741)
    - Santa Monica (continued). Long Wharf; Sunset Park, undated (Box 24, Item 1742-1743)
    - Long Beach homes and buildings including Cerritos Ranch, 1885; undated (Box 24, Item 1744-1748)
    - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfrey's numbers. Miscellaneous Los Angeles and Los Angeles County, 1874; undated (Box 47, Item 2513-2520)
  - Pasadena and San Gabriel Valley
    - Pasadena, 1887-1904; undated (Box 1, Item 109-129)
    - Pasadena. Busch Gardens, 1909-1914; undated; [Includes Graham Photo Co. photographs.] (Box 1, Item 130-150)
    - Pasadena. Busch Gardens; Busch Residence, 1914; undated; [Includes Graham Photo Co. photographs.] (Box 2, Item 151-170)
    - Pasadena. Busch Gardens; fairy tale scenes, ca. 1910; undated; [Includes Graham Photo Co. photographs.] (Box 2, Item 171-182)
    - San Gabriel Valley. Baldwin's Ranch; Arcadia; San Gabriel; Monrovia; Duarte; Pomona, ca. 1890; undated; [Includes photographs taken by William H. Fletcher.] (Box 2, Item 183-197)
    - San Fernando; San Gabriel; Eagle Rock; Pasadena; Los Angeles hotels, 1884-1919; undated (Box 7, Item 933-953)
    - Arroyo Seco, Pasadena and Glendale including views of the Raymond Hotel and the Ostrich Farm, 1872; undated (Box 20, Item 1614-1621a)
    - Pasadena, San Marino and Sierra Madre including the Lake Vineyard, Sunnyslope, El Molino Viejo and various street scenes, orchards and vineyards, 1871; 1885,; 1921,; undated (Box 21, Item 1622-1652)
    - Various San Gabriel Valley scenes, including Santa Anita Ranch, 1872; undated (Box 21, Item 1653-1662)
    - Rowland Property, 1921; undated (Box 21, Item 1663-1665)
    - El Monte region, including Savannah and Ellis Family Property, 1908-1920; undated (Box 22, Item 1666-1678a)
    - Pomona buildings, street scenes and open land, includes Palomares Hotel and fire, 1880-1890; 1911,; undated (Box 22, Item 1679-1694)
    - Spadra homes and ranches, including the Rubottom home and hotel, undated (Box 22, Item 1695-1699)
    - Spadra (continued), includes "Monkey Town" newspaper clipping, 1885; 1919,; undated (Box 23, Item 1700-1702)
    - San Gabriel Mission, undated (Box 30, Item 2024-2027)
    - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfrey's numbers. Rubottom property, Spadra, 1874; undated (Box 46, Item 2483-2486)
    - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfrey's numbers. San Gabriel Valley, undated (Box 47, Item 2500-2512)
  - Orange County
    - Orange County. Arch Beach; Laguna Beach, ca. 1915, undated; undated (Box 1, Item 1-34)
    - Madame Modjeska's home; Orange County; San Diego; Riverside; Missions, 1901-1902; undated (Box 1, Item 40-59)
    - Orange County. Santa Ana, street scenes, buildings, and residences, 1873; 1898,; undated (Box 28, Item 1898-1906)
    - Orange County. Santa Ana scenes and residences, including Santa Ana Depot, Opera House, undated (Box 29, Item 1907-1911)
    - Orange County. Anaheim street scenes and buildings; Anaheim Landing, undated (Box 29, Item 1912-1922)
    - Orange County. Buena Park; Fullerton; Miscellaneous, undated (Box 29, Item 1923-1929)
    - Vischer illustrations. Locations from Orange County to Paso Robles, 1860s; undated (Box 33, Item 2110-2120)
    - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfrey's numbers. San Luis Rey and San Juan Capistrano Missions, undated (Box 47, Item 2496-2499)
  - Riverside County
    - Riverside County. Tibbetts property; Lake Elsinore, 1923; undated (Box 29, Item 1930-1932)
  - San Bernardino County
    - San Bernardino County. Includes city of San Bernardino buildings and street scenes, 1873-1874; 1883,; undated; [Includes photographs taken by W.A. Vale.] (Box 29, Item 1933-1948)
  - San Diego County
    - San Diego County; Imperial Valley, 1880s; 1894,; undated (Box 6, Item 786-799)
    - San Diego, 1872; undated; [Includes photographs taken by J.C. Parker.] (Box 29, Item 1949-1951)
    - San Diego buildings and street scenes; Views of San Diego Harbor; Drawings from Phoenixiana; Other miscellaneous, 1874; undated; [Includes photographs taken by J.C. Parker.] (Box 30, Item 1952-1977)
    - San Diego Mission and surrounding grounds, 1874; undated; [Includes photographs taken by J.C. Parker.] (Box 31, Item 2012-2023)
    - W.M. Godfrey photographs organized by Godfrey's numbers. San Luis Rey and San Juan Capistrano Missions, undated (Box 47, Item 2496-2499)
  - Ventura County
    - Camulos Rancho; Santa Cruz; Ventura County; Automobile related photographs in Los Angeles, 1860; 1894-1920, undated; undated (Box 9, Item 1097-1123)
    - Ventura County and Paso Robles, including Camulos Ranch, undated (Box 30, Item 1978-1980)
  - Santa Barbara County
    - Santa Barbara and Santa Barbara County, undated (Box 30, Item 1981-1984)
  - Monterey County
    - City of Monterey, buildings and homes, 1850; undated (Box 30, Item 1985-1991)
  - Santa Cruz County
    - Santa Cruz County. Benicia and Big Basin, 1857; 1918, undated; undated (Box 32, Item 1992-1997)
    - Santa Cruz County. Big Basin; Santa Cruz; Other miscellaneous, ca. 1856; 1918,; undated (Box 31, Item 1998-2003)
  - Marin County
    - San Francisco and Petaluma drawings and photos, includes Baldwin Hotel, M.G. Vallejo Adobe, 1849; 1865,; undated (Box 31, Item 2004-2011)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Southwest scenery; Los Angeles transportation, 1912; 1915,; undated (Box 4, Item 429-448)
    - Miscellaneous scenery, undated (Box 10, Item 1252-1257)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 10, Item 1258-1263)
    - Miscellaneous. Unidentified locations, undated (Box 43, Item 2396-2413)
    - Miscellaneous. Unidentified buildings, houses, landscapes, undated (Box 34, Item 2414-2458)
- Subject List
  - Adobes
    - Missions; Adobes, 1890-1931; undated (Box 6, Item 800-826)
    - Los Angeles. Avila Adobe/Stockton's Headquarters, undated (Box 11, Item 1292-1295)
    - Los Angeles. Homes and buildings along San Pedro Street including the Lugo adobe, 1921; undated (Box 16, Item 1431-1436)
    - San Francisco and Petaluma drawings and photos, includes Baldwin Hotel, M.G. Vallejo Adobe, 1849; 1865,; undated (Box 31, Item 2004-2011)
  - Agriculture
    - San Diego County; Imperial Valley, 1880s; 1894,; undated (Box 6, Item 786-799)
    - Wolfskill Ranch orchards and fruit trees, undated (Box 15, Item 1413-1415)
    - Los Angeles. Farms and homes on future site of the Southern Branch of the University of California, undated (Box 19, Item 1580-1584)
    - North East and South East Central Los Angeles including Aliso Street; the Sainsevains property; Beaudry Reservoir; Boyle Heights, 1875; undated (Box 20, Item 1586-1600)
    - Various San Gabriel Valley scenes, including Santa Anita Ranch, 1872; undated (Box 21, Item 1653-1662)
    - Orange County. Buena Park; Fullerton; Miscellaneous, undated (Box 29, Item 1923-1929)
    - Ventura County and Paso Robles, including Camulos Ranch, undated (Box 30, Item 1978-1980)
  - Churches